

Rithik Banerjee

.Net Developer

Passionate software developer with around one year of experience in .Net framework, that includes understanding system requirements, designing architecture, development, testing, updating and support of commercial application. Extensive knowledge in object oriented programming, web development, database management and version control.

banerjee13rithik@gmail.com

rithikbanerjee.github.io/profile

twitter.com/banerjee_rithik

github.com/RithikBanerjee

(+91) 990 347 1021 / 890 206 1169

linkedin.com/in/RithikBanerjee

live:banerjee13rithik

stackoverflow.com/users/13430233

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Kredent InfoEdge 🗷

09/2020 - Present Kolkata, West Bengal Full Time Software Developer responsible for maintaining and versioninga stock analysis application

- Added features as well as resolved issues of our web/android/iOS application named StockEdge. C

Contact: Arindam Mukherjee - +91 83370 43077

Web Developer

Opticodes Technologies 🗷

07/2019 - 09/2020

Kanpur, Uttar Pradesh Full Time Web Developer responsible for planning architecture, coding, versioning and maintaining a GST based portal.

- Worked on income tax filing portal, MyTaxCafe & GST returns filing portal, MyGSTCafe. 🗹
- Developed custom modules and components namely, Query Creator, Dapper Method Store, Request Handler, Validation Engine, Auora etc.
- Created GST, E-invoice and E-way bill generating portal using NIC API's.

Contact: Abhishek Sharma - +91 84008 90312

TECHNICAL SKILLS



PROJECTS

Aleph (04/2020 - 07/2020) 🗹

Music playing web application based on Django framework.

Excel Data Importer (01/2020 - 03/2020) 🗹

- ORM module to import excel data based on .Net framework.

GSP SDK (11/2019 - 02/2020) [7]

Goods & Services Tax module based on Rest APIs.

Iris Detector (09/2018 - 04/2019) 3

Python module used in iris based bio-metric authentication.

EDUCATION

B. Tech in Computer Science

Jalpaiguri Government Engineering College (MAKAUT) 🕝

2015 - 2019 Jalpaiguri, West Bengal

HOBBIES

Article Writing 🛂 Author at C#Corner.

Competitive Coding 🗹

Certified in Problem Solving, Rest API, Python, Java & JS.

Higher Secondary

National Gems Higher Secondary School (CISCE) 🗷

2013 - 2015 Kolkata, West Bengal

LANGUAGES

English Full Professional Proficiency Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency